{"data":[{"question":"Water on the earth is being recycled continuously in a process is known as the hydrologic cycle.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the earth","b":"is being recycled","c":"continuously","d":"is known","answer":"4","explain":"- Is known-> known","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Every morning, I walked to school with my neighbor John, who is also my classmate.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"walked","b":"with","c":"neighbor","d":"also","answer":"1","explain":"- Walked-> walks","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"This groundwater is extremely important to life on earth, since 95 percent of the earth's water is in the ocean and are too salty for human beings or plants.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"extremely","b":"to","c":"are","d":"for","answer":"3","explain":"- Are-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Chemicals liked sulfuric acid and soda were manufactured long before man began to understand the nature of the atom.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"liked","b":"were","c":"long","d":"began","answer":"1","explain":"- Liked-> like","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Most of the models were given for me over the years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Most","b":"models","c":"for","d":"over","answer":"3","explain":"- For-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Dent station is situated on the Seatle to Carliste railway line, said be the most scenic in the country.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is situated","b":"railway line","c":"be","d":"the most scenic","answer":"3","explain":"- Be-> to be","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"We have never stayed in such the expensive hotel before.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have","b":"never","c":"the","d":"before","answer":"3","explain":"- The-> a","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"A fire has destroyed most of the old city of London in the 1600s.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"has destroyed","c":"the old city","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"- Has destroyed-> destroyed","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The manager was very astounding when they told him about the robbery.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"astounding","c":"when","d":"about","answer":"2","explain":"- Astounding-> astaunded","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Winners were greatly honored by having olive wreaths placed on their heads and having poems singing about their deeds.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"honored","b":"having","c":"placed","d":"singing","answer":"4","explain":"- Singing-> sing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}